## **Alexandra Purfield**

3300 E 14th Ave Denver, CO 80206 (303) 304-0994 alexpurfield@gmail.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Vertafore**, Denver — *Product Specialist/ Account Manager*

October 2021 - August 2023

Conducted product demonstrations for ReferenceConnect, collaborating with customers to tailor technology solutions to their unique business needs.

### **Procare Solutions**, Denver — *Marketing Development Rep*

May 2021 - October 2021

Contracting position as a marketing development representative, working with internal systems and other departments to qualify leads for childcare software. Also provided similar contract work for FoodMaven December-March of 2020.

## **Gusto**, Denver — Onboarding Submissions Expert/ Customer Service Rep

October 2019 - October 2020

Initiated as a contractor in Onboarding Submissions, transitioned to a full-time role as a Customer Service Representative during the initial year of the Covid-19 pandemic.

### **Moes Original BBQ,** Englewood — Bartender/ Bar Manager

August 2015 - January 2019

Managed front-of-house operations, including live music shows, bowling leagues, parties, and diverse events while serving as a bartender.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **University of Denver**, Denver — Full Stack Coding Boot Camp

August 2023 - November 2023

Full-time rigorous curriculum that covers a full stack, including HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, progressive web apps, agile methodology, computer science, database theory, MongoDB, MySQL, and Git.Graduated with a 97% overall grade.

# **Metropolitan State University of Denver**, Denver — Technical Communication, Emphasis in Writing and Editing

September 2014 - May 2019

Received a Bachelors of Science Degree in Technical Communications with an emphasis in writing and editing and received a 3.5 GPA overall.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, progressive web apps, agile methodology, computer science, database theory, MongoDB, MySQL, and Git.

#### **Summary**

My name is Alex Purfield and I am interested in pursuing a career as a Junior Web Developer. My background has primarily been in people-facing positions such as sales and customer support however technology and software has always been the great equalizer across my experiences. I am a recent graduate of the DU Full-Stack Coding Bootcamp where I honed my problem-solving skills and officially caught what my instructor called, "the coding bug". I enjoy the meticulous process of debugging and the satisfaction of overcoming the challenges and want to continue expanding my knowledge in the coding world.